<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <record id="shipment_order_data" model="shipment.order.data">
        <field name="ship_conf">SHIPMENT ORDER</field>
        <field name="title_name">REFERENCE</field>
        <field name="ship_date" >DATE</field>
        <field name="ship_to" >TO</field>
        <field name="ship_type" >SHIPMENT TYPE</field>
        <field name="package_name">PACKAGE NAME</field>
        <field name="package_desc" >CARGO DETAIL</field>
        <field name="package_qty" >PACKAGE QTY</field>
        <field name="temp_deg">TEMPERATURE DEGREES</field>
        <field name="package_vendor" >PACKAGE VENDOR</field>
        <field name="package_con">CONSIGNEE</field>
        <field name="ekso_condi">INCOTERMS CONDITION</field>
        <field name="package_valid_until">VALID UNTIL</field>
        <field name="package_rt_name">ROUTE MANAGER</field>
        <field name="condi_route">CONDITION AND ROUTE</field>
        <field name="package_cost">COST</field>
        <field name="border">Border</field>
        <field name="transport_agent">TRANSPORT NAME</field>
        <field name="costumer_name">COSTUMER NAME</field>
        <field name="agent_name" >NAME:Bayarkhuu</field>
        <field name="cos_name">NAME:Uyanga</field>
        <field name="sign" >SIGN</field>
        <field name="notice" >NOTICE</field>
        <field name="condi_text">CONDITION TEXT</field>
        <field name="condi_texts">
            The present “Shipment confrmation” is considered as a freight agreement between Monlogistics Worldwide (MLW)and Tianjin Well-Carry Logistics Co.,Ltd (agent).
            By accepting this confrmation, MLW’s nominated agent undertakes a responsibility to deliver the cargo within estimated time to a named port/border to respect an agreement with cargoes actual consignee.
            In case of unforeseen additional charges occurred at the port/border/station, the agent is responsible to advise MLW prior the cargoes arrival at destination or cargo release to consignee. Any additional charges must be proved by documents.
            MLW and its agent will exchange cargoes tracing information in daily fashion including special notices and demurrage standard of used equipment, informing each other about a release instruction and necessary documents in relation to transit customs formality, to avoid cargoes excessive delay at transit port or border station and related hereto charges.
            MLW’s agent should send the freight invoice before the cargo arrival to the fnal destination.
            MLW’s agent shall be responsible to instruct the shipper about cargoes proper loading and fxing into equipment, in order to avoid further charges to correct and balance the loading.
            MLW’s agent is aware of fnancial policy of MLW, that the payment for all operations shall be made upon agent’s invoice confrmation and confrmed “Shipment confrmation”.
            MLW and its agent shall respect the interests of each other and will not disclose any part of this agreement to third party without authorization of contractual counterpart.
            MLW’s agent should pay high attention to top priority cargoes.</field> 
         <field name="locale">1</field>
    </record>
 </odoo> 